Gonzalo Hernández Full Stack Developer

Madrid, Spain

4 658 836 097

in linkedin.com/in/ghgarcia/



github.com/hernandezgonzalo



Profile

Hi! I'm Gonzalo, graduated in Advertising and Public Relations and a Higher Technician in Computer Systems Management. I have more than ten years of experience in Digital Marketing. I have recently finished a Web Development Bootcamp at Ironhack.

I consider myself a versatile and responsible person, who possesses self-discipline, is deadline orientated and has the enthusiasm and ambition to complete projects to the highest standard. A quick learner who can absorb new ideas and can communicate clearly and effectively. In the future I would like to keep growing professionally as a MERN Stack JavaScript Developer.

Professional Experience

Making Golf

01/2019 - present Madrid, Spain

Head of the Digital Marketing Department

 Responsible for the visual identity and digital communication of the group companies

10/2012 - 12/2018

Madrid, Spain

Front-end Web Developer and Digital Marketing Specialist

- Web development (HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, PHP, MySQL, WordPress)
- SEO, SEM and Web Analytics
- Social Media (CM) and Social Ads
- Email Marketing

08/2010 - 10/2012

Madrid, Spain

Graphic Web Designer

- Illustration and layout
- Web development (HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Flash)
- · Photography and video editing

04/2006 - 11/2008

Madrid, Spain

COMPOSAN Industrial y Tecnología, Information Technology Technician

Helpdesk support and network management

Skills

JavaScript, React, Redux, React Native, Node.js, Express, MongoDB, Mongoose, HTML, CSS, SASS, ¡Query, Handlebars, AJAX, WebSockets, Bootstrap, Material-UI, Git, TypeScript

Education

10/2019 - 04/2020 **Ironhack**, Web Development Bootcamp

JavaScript - HTML - CSS - Sass - Node.js - Express - MongoDB - React

2013 - 2018 **Universidad Rey Juan Carlos**, Advertising and Public Relations



Versatility, responsibility, verbal communication, open-mindedness, analysis, organization and design.



Spanish English ————

Projects

04/2020 - 04/2020

COVID-19 Pandemic Statistics, *Application to keep track of coronavirus cases*
Final project to be made during the Ironhack Web Development Bootcamp. It is a full-stack web application developed in Javascript with React and Node.js.

of Interests

Music, sports, technology and astronomy.